<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tour Guide App</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="shwedagon">The Shwedagon Pagoda (Burmese: ရွှေတိဂုံဘုရား), officially named Shwedagon Zedi Daw (Burmese: ရွှေတိဂုံစေတီတော်) and also known as the Great Dagon Pagoda and the Golden Pagoda, is a gilded stupa located in Yangon, Myanmar. The 99-metre-tall (325 ft)[1] pagoda is situated on Singuttara Hill, to the west of Kandawgyi Lake, and dominates the Yangon skyline.</string>
    <string name="kyaiktiyo">Kyaiktiyo Pagoda (Burmese: ကျိုက်ထီးရိုးဘုရား; also known as Golden Rock) is a well-known Buddhist pilgrimage site in Mon State, Burma. It is a small pagoda (7.3 metres (24 ft)) built on the top of a granite boulder covered with gold leaves pasted on by its male devotees.</string>
    <string name="shwenandaw_monastery">Shwenandaw Monastery (Burmese: ရွှေနန်းတော်ကျောင်း; lit. "Golden Palace Monastery") is a historic Buddhist monastery located near Mandalay Hill, Mandalay Region, Myanmar (formerly Burma).</string>
    <string name="bagan">Bagan (Burmese: ပုဂံ) is an ancient city located in the Mandalay Region of Myanmar. From the 9th to 13th centuries, the city was the capital of the Pagan Kingdom, the first kingdom that unified the regions that would later constitute modern Myanmar. During the kingdom\'s height between the 11th and 13th centuries, over 10,000 Buddhist temples, pagodas and monasteries were constructed in the Bagan plains alone, of which the remains of over 2,200 temples and pagodas still survive to the present day.</string>
    <string name="maruk_u">Mrauk U (Burmese: မြောက်‌ဦးမြို့; formerly known as Myohaung) is an archaeologically important town in northern Rakhine State, Myanmar. It is also the capital of Mrauk-U Township, a sub region of the Mrauk-U District. From 1430 until 1785, it was the capital of the Mrauk U Kingdom, the most important and powerful Rakhine (Arakanese) kingdom.</string>
    <string name="inle_lake">Inle Lake (Burmese: အင်းလေးကန်), is a freshwater lake located in the Nyaungshwe Township of Taunggyi District of Shan State, part of Shan Hills in Myanmar (Burma). It is the second largest lake in Myanmar with an estimated surface area of 44.9 square miles (116 km2), and one of the highest at an elevation of 2,900 feet (880 m). During the dry season, the average water depth is 7 feet (2.1 m), with the deepest point being 12 feet (3.7 m), but during the rainy season this can increase by 5 feet (1.5 m).</string>
</resources>
